h2o.ai 2019-12-12

# Privacy - Open Source Leader in AI and ML

### H2O Privacy Policy

H2O.ai, Inc. (“H2O”) knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy practices (“Privacy Policy”). By using the H2O services, or visiting www.h2o.ai, (collectively, the “Services”) you accept the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

#### What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers H2O’s treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that H2O gathers when you access or use the Services. This Privacy Policy does not cover use of information by third parties we do not control.

#### What Personal Information Does H2O Collect?

We collect the following types of information from our end users:

**Information You Provide to Us:**

We may receive and store any information you enter into our website and/or otherwise provide when you use the Services. For example:

  * Name
  * Company name
  * Postal address
  * Telephone number
  * Email address
  * If you participate in one of our giveaways or promotions, your t-shirt size, as applicable
  * Social media account ID
  * Content (text, images, messages, comments or any other kind of content that is not your e-mail address) you may post on our Websites, including blogs available on our Websites
  * Information about your company’s systems
  * Information about your company’s interests and potential or actual use of the Platform Services.
  * Any personal information contained within the data that you may make available to or load into the Platform Services
  * Employment application information

#### Cookies

We may implement cookies on the www.h2o.ai website. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies may be required to use our website. We use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies.

#### HOW DOES H2O USE PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We only use your Personal Information internally to: (i) provide Services to our users and (ii) further develop and improve such Services.

Personal Information about our end users is an integral part of our business. We do not rent, sell or disclose your Personal Information to anyone – except for the following limited purposes:

_Agents_ : We may employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf – meaning they are helping us provide our Services. We may share your Personal Information with such companies/persons solely as necessary for them to help us provide the Services. Unless we tell you differently, H2O’s agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us.

_Business Transfers_ : In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if H2O, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that H2O goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party.

_Protection of H2O and Others_ : We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of H2O, our employees, our users, or others.

_With Your Consent_ : Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

#### CONDITIONS OF USE

If you decide to access or use the Services, any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and any other applicable written agreement between you and H2O, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.

#### What Choices Do I Have?

You may request deletion of your Personal Information by sending an e-mail to [privacy@h2o.ai](mailto:privacy@h2o.ai). Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

H2O may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting the new privacy statement on our website at [https://www.h2o.ai/privacy](https://www.h2o.ai/privacy/). Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such notice has been provided.

#### Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy in connection with the Services, please send us a detailed message at [privacy@h2o.ai](mailto:privacy@h2o.ai). We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

Effective Date: Oct 20th, 2016

H2O Legal & Privacy  
2307 Leghorn St  
Mountain View, CA 94043  
Telephone: +1 (650) 227- 4572  
Email: [privacy@h2o.ai](mailto:privacy@h2o.ai)
